Would you like some wine?
Uh, w-well...
Do you have oolong tea?
Yes, I'll go prepare some.
- I'll have cider!
- I'll have a Bireley's!
How about you?
I'll... I'll have a Bireley's, too.
Another Bireley's, please!
Cheers!
Sounds like the bride
Naoko-san's quite the drinker...
Bad news for the groom, Akagawa!
His face is already beet red!
Although I'm ashamed to
admit I was out of my element,
I wanted to plunge into the
alluring world of adulthood.
In other words, I wanted to not
be held back by my seniors
and to drink as much as I possibly could!
You're still not tired of staring at her?
I... I was just looking that
way by chance, all right?
I was completely head over heels for her.
She had grabbed hold of my heart
when she joined my club as my junior,
and ever since that day, I've committed
myself to the SEE Strategy!
The SEE Strategy
Senpai, what a coincidence!
I was just passing through by chance!
Such a coincidence!
By chance!
Coincidence...
Chance!
Coinc...
Co...
Chance!
My goal was to appear in front
of her as frequently as possible,
and thus, the SEE strategy involves
being Seen, Everytime, Everywhere.
Seen, Everytime, Everywhere
This ensures our meetings push
beyond the realm of mere chance,
and she'll have no choice
but to feel the red string of fate!
My chance is ripening!
What I need now is the courage to wait!
That's not exactly courage.
Stop reading my mind!
You're so obsessed over removing
obstacles in your path...
Shall you live under the apple tree
you're planting beside yourself?
The School Festival Executive Director,
and also, my friend.
The School Festival Executive Director
The most photographed person on campus,
he receives the most Valentine's
chocolate in all Sakyo-ku.
He also puts his beauty to
use through cross-dressing,
and his infamy rose after confusing several
young men during the Fall Festival.
You dithering fool!
She's right in front of your face,
yet you do nothing!
Hey now, you're drinking too much.
Meet my other friend,
Don Underwear
who six months ago vowed to never change
his underwear until his wish came true.
Despite smashing the
previous record for doing so,
and earning the glorious
title of "Don Underwear",
his wish is as yet unfulfilled.
Leave it alone already!
I'll strike when MY iron is hot!
Your iron, huh...
Tonight's my chance!
If I sit at the same table as her
when we go to the next place,
I can push things to
the next stage for sure!
Not romantic!
Now then, we'll be heading
off to the next pub!
Anyone who is staying with
our group, please follow me!
It will be a 3 minute walk,
so take care not to lose sight!
You're all coming, right?
Right?!
In the neighborhood of Shijo-Kiyamachi,
men and women indulging in evening
pleasures came in an incessant stream.
Here of all places would have what I seek,
an encounter with glorious alcohol!
The dazzling world of adulthood awaits!
The Night is Short, Walk On Girl
One pina colada, please!
I had a fondness for cocktails.
Picking a cocktail was like
picking out a sparkling jewel,
everything about it felt so luxurious.
In all honesty, the entire Pacific
Ocean could be rum for all I care,
that's how much I adore rum.
I long to down the entire bottle
the second I lay hands on one,
but this is the sort of dream
one best be discreet about.
Hey you, looks like you
can hold your drink.
Your next one's on me.
Oh no! That's fine!
Get this gal an Acapulco!
Rum's made from sugarcane...
Brandy was originally known
as vin brule, or "burnt wine".
Once you distill wine,
the alcohol content skyrockets,
and that's how you end up
with brandy and whisky.
You certainly know a lot...
Just part of gettin' old.
I'm sorry I won't be able to keep up.
Nah, spending time with
people I pass by in the night,
that's where I find my joy.
There's a legendary drink out
there called Fake Denki Bran.
"Fake"?
Denki Bran was cooked up by a well-known
joint in Asakusa back in the 1800s...
It's a cocktail gone down in history.
It's so famous you can find
the stuff in convenience stores,
but the recipe was kept
under lock-and-key for ages.
However, some time ago,
some guy working for
Kyoto Central Telephone
got the bright idea to
try replicating its flavor.
After traveling down blind
alleys of trial-and-error,
what he discovered at
the end of his journey,
that's what's now known
as Fake Denki Bran.
Both its taste and its scent,
they're totally different from Denki Bran,
but the mysterious and
enticing flavor it DOES have,
you can tell it's still being
made in secret somewhere,
and being smuggled through
the streets as we speak.
I'd really like to give it a try...
You're a girl after my own heart!
Hey, you!
We've got some good girls if you're lost!
I'm fine.
- A raven-haired maiden is my goal!
- So, raven hair is what you're after...
- That's not what I meant!
- Don't take this personally.
Looking at you brings back
memories of my daughter.
I was never the greatest father to her...
Been a while since we met face-to-face.
Not like I got the right to see her anyway...
This is one of the most
important days of her life...
And I stood her up...
Young lady!!!
Never forget to grab onto
happiness with your own hands!
Find out what's valuable and hold tight!
Yes!
Go and give it your all!
- Give it your all...
- Yes!
G-Give it your all...!
Todo-san...
Give it your all --
Well, you sure showed him!
Oh? Well, this is rather shameless.
Th-This is erotic art!
I'm an art collector, damn it!
Todo's well-known for
being a gross old pervert...
He's just a piece of shit
from top to bottom.
A grope here or there
ain't gonna hurt anything!
You shouldn't so easily put your faith
in people you chance by out at night.
Of course, I'm referring to US as well.
He's part of some gross group called
the Bedchamber Investigation Team,
all he does is collect
that perverted stuff!
I hear his business has plunged these days,
and he's plunged himself
into debt as a result...
Well, it's not for me to know how
the vulgar masses live their lives.
But I didn't know that then,
and I still did something awful.
It's fine, it's fine!
BE more awful and cold-hearted!
But y'know, you sure have
one hell of a punch...
That's what I call my Friendship Punch.
My mother taught it to
me when I was little.
Do you understand?
As you make your way through this world,
you will find the noble amount to a handful.
What's left are utter fools and rotten fiends,
or quite possibly utterly foolish rotten fiends.
Such encounters are when you
must use the Friendship Punch.
When you wrap your thumb
in your four fingers like so,
your fist becomes like the
warm paw of the Beckoning Cat...
Such a fist can no longer truly
convey feelings of hatred.
Thus, we are freed from the chains of violence,
and thus we invite harmony into this world.
This is my trump card,
the only technique my parents permit
me to use on the outside world.
You certainly seem wise beyond your years!
Perhaps you'd like to join us tonight?
We'll show you how things
are done in Pontocho!
I would love that!
But, I don't have any more money...
No need to worry.
It's been many years since
I'VE had money either.
Put it on Todo's tab, okay?
Money is indeed quite nomadic.
If you mark some, it's not unheard of
to come across it again in your life.
Looks like Rihaku-san
is up to his old tricks...
You've heard of him,
the crazy old loan shark?
The one who goes around in
that luxurious 3-story tall train!
He's a big collector of
old books and antiques...
And apparently, the underwear
stolen off young men!
Ew, Higuchi! Wearing used
pants like that is totally gross!
He also has quite the collection
of a drink called Fake Denki Bran.
The one from the legend...?
But this worked out well.
Higuchi-kun doesn't wear any underwear!
Excuse me, would anyone...?
Would anyone happen to have underwear?
Damn it...
Why's this gotta happen to me...
Hey, young'n!
You lookin' for some help?
Yes!!!
Some underwear, please!!!
Then get up here and help
me drown my sorrows!
We're gonna get plastered...
Now take a good look and
see how she does things.
Yay!!!
Who are you?!
Who cares, are you out for a drink?
- Yay!
- I-I am...
Sounds like fun!
Let's go down all of
the booze in Kiyamachi!
Yay!
- Yaaaay!!!
- Let's go!
We've breached the walls, and we mustn't hesitate.
Shame will only give you away here.
Waltzing in uninvited is a test of one's will --
Will you sink, or will you swim?
Rhetoric Club
So you just want to be
a spectator, my dear?
Why are you...
Licking my ear?!
If you don't have talent, then work hard!
Working hard REQUIRES talent!
And therefore...
Enough of this! You don't know anything!
Just WHAT is going on here?
The chaos from arguing for argument's sake.
That's not it at all!
It's called rhetoric!
Oh, and you...
Which is better, marrying the man
you love or the one you don't?
The man you DON'T love is a far better choice!
Once love enters the picture,
one loses all sense of reason.
Choosing the man you don't love
is a choice made from pure logic!
This is a life-long decision, after all,
so it needs to be a rational decision
born strictly from prudence!
These so-called feelings of love,
they can't be explained with any rationality!
They shouldn't be part of
marriage in the first place!
Feelings of love will never cool for one
you never felt love for in the first place!
Infidelity won't burden
you with shame and jealousy!
Rationality practically demands that women
should marry men they don't love...
- So why DO they marry for love...
- We're at this guy's farewell party!
He got jilted and he's off to study in London!
Damn it!!!
Who the hell wants to go to England?!
Naoko-san...!!!
Now then!
Let us celebrate the future prospects
of our senpai Kousaka in London!
The Dance of the Sophists, begin!!!
Senpai! Go off and become a great man!
Become a great man, forget your
problems, and never come back here!
Don't worry, Senpai, we'll be fine without you!
Thank you!!!
It's an immense joy being sent
off by gentlemen like you!
Shall we head off to Pontocho now?
- Well, hello!
- My, it HAS been a while!
This is a 60th birthday celebration.
That's wonderful! You wanna drink?
- My son's wedding was today.
- Even better, let's drink!
Life is over much too soon...
What is life, anyway.
It's literally one's lifespan, is it not?
- So at the end of life is death?
- No, the opposite!
So what do we call the end of life?
Let's treat life and one's
lifespan as different, shall we?
Well this is a drag.
No one's touching any of the
Akadama Punch I brought...
Higuchi-kun, you know some tricks!
Come on, liven up this party!
Well, the tension in the room is a tad thick,
but I'll try my Higuchi-Style Flying Technique.
- Boring...
- Why's he wearing pants?
My spectators...
...Are worse off than I thought.
I wish it was more lively in here...
Us oldsters are running out of time!
The hours are only getting faster...
Young lady, you mind if I see your watch?
- Oh, my!
- It's so slow!
Isn't this normal?
This is what ours look like.
DAYS
And see how that compares to ours!
YEARS
Time certainly does fly...
You're keeping a good pace!
Huh?!
You, you polished off
all of these, didn't you!
You can sure hold your stuff!
I drink until there's nothing left!
She's the real deal...
I may be plain, unpolished,
and less interesting than a rice cooker,
But here and now, I demand
you all point and laugh!
C'mon, what the heck are you doing?
That's... That's the Dance of the Sophists!
The Dance of the Sophists
we dreamed up so long ago!
Okay, everyone, join in!
This! This is from those lazy days
we spent dabbling in rhetoric!
This takes me back!
Us! Exactly like eels!
Slippery and slimy, no one could pin us down!
It appears that she's this
evening's leading lady.
To think that such a
tradition would live on today!
The cherished desire of any
alumni of the Rhetoric Club!
Well, let's keep it going, this Dance
of Burdens to the Next Generation!
Now, drink up!
A talent like yours only comes every 100 years!
You should match your skills against Rihaku!
With him? Yes, she could!
If you win against him,
he'll grant any wish you ask!
You could drink Fake Denki Bran
to your heart's content...
If he wants a fight, I'll give it.
I'd bet on you to win for sure!
- Me, too!
- And me as well!
C'mon, ain't you gonna drink with me?!
Chug! Chug!
Uh, I don't know about
being forced to chug...
Who gives a shit!?
I'm gonna be forcin' you, anyway!
Back in the '80s bubble,
I was rollin' in dough...
Now, that's just a far-off dream...
The final blow was that
tornado the other day...
Whirling down from Fushimi Castle,
it came roaring towards
my koi carp nursery!
All of my beloved koi were sucked up,
sent swirling into the night sky!
Yuko!!!
Jirokichi!!!
Damn you!!!
Gimme back Yuko!
Gimme back Jirokichi!!!
Um, excuse me...
Could I get that underwear now...?
You think a scum-sucking student
like you DESERVES underwear?!
I got to where I was by bustin' my ass
through my own naked merits...
Damn it!!!
Todo-san!
Is it true you're giving
away your collection?
Go away!!!
I got it rough, y'know?!
May I have a look?
And these are such
splendid ones, too...
Hey, young man!
You're lookin' like you
wanna call me a creep!
I'm not saying anything!
We're the Bedchamber Investigation Team,
we only seek to gather artifacts
of our sensual cultural heritage!
"What ya really mean
is you collect porn!"
That's what you wanna say, right?!
I'm not saying anything!!!
That asshole's comin' after my collection...
He offered me that sweet loan,
which tore my daughter away from me...
And now he's tearin' away my
erotic art, the only friend I got left!
When will Rihaku-san get here?
He's gonna be here any minute now...
All right!
I'll go contact everyone in Bedchamber!
We'll all come send these ladies
off with one final viewing!
Thank you!!!
Thank you...
You're comin' too!
Over here!
Okay!
Rihaku, come out and play...
Rihaku, come out and play!
No, you're doing it all wrong!!!
Leave ALL your shame behind!
Yo!!!
Rihaku, come out and play!
What's this?!
Would you look at that!
It just sort of happened!
Naoko-san!!!
Yasuo!!!
Such a tragic loss!
This is a hard reset on
cultural anthropology!
"Why are grown men cryin'
their asses off over erotic art!!!"
That's the kinda look
you got in your eyes!
For the last time, I don't care!
You self-conscious or something?
It sounds like some hero is
challenging Rihaku to a drink off.
What, they got no self-preservation?
Yeah, they're runnin' around
Kiyamachi tearin' the place apart!
I heard they're 6 meters tall!
A giant wearing a ragged old yukata!
I hear they can shoot koi out of their mouth!
They came here all the
way from far-off Oshu!
Less a hero, more a monster!
A sleeping giant!
A fallen monk!
Who on earth are YOU people?!
Just those who wield rhetoric
to become slippery like eels!
My love is happy.
And knowing that, I am happy too!
Banzai!
Banzai...
What's going on up there?
No, I'm ruined!!!
Todo-san! Don't give in to despair!
It doesn't matter!
That ol' bastard's gonna kill me for sure!
How picturesque!
Dad?!
Naoko!!!
- I'm gonna die of shame here!!!
- Knock it off already, Dad!
I don't care if you're a big perv!
Naoko-san!!!
Kousaka-kun...?!
I'm begging you!
Please, marry me instead!
If you truly love that man,
I'm begging you to not marry him!
Yes, you've been over this...
No idea what your point is, though...
Kousaka, you're an
embarrassment to men!
Why are you still in Japan?
At last, he takes the stage.
Rihaku
Todo-san. It's been a while.
Where are the goods?
That punk kid there ruined them!!!
- Man, that's gross...
- Totally...
So you haven't kept your word.
How do you plan on settling your debts now?
He's gonna kill me!!!
Why don't you come on board.
Wait right there!
Huh?! It's you...!
Todo-san! You mustn't give up!
There's always another
move on the board!
You?! But why...
I'm the guy who threw around
erotic art and felt you up!
However...
You still introduced me to
a wonderful way to view life.
Rihaku-san!
I shall be your opponent tonight...
I challenge you to a drinking contest!
And I will most certainly be the victor.
Quite the development...
...As you wish.
My underwear...!!!
This floor is the bathhouse,
the banquet hall is below.
Fake Denki Bran.
Alcohol as transparent as pure water.
If I prove victorious, his debt is doubled.
You know there's no mercy?
If you so allow me, I shall act as judge.
Now then, begin!!!
The taste of Fake Denki Bran
is life's meaninglessness.
To me, the taste is like being filled
from top to bottom with life's warmth...
Luxurious and abundant.
You're a brat who knows nothing of life.
Life is empty...
Plentiful.
Truly empty...
Life is isolation and hollowness,
gone in an instant.
Life is nothing but taking.
Giving.
Anguish.
Joy.
So why are you out tonight?
I'm only following my thread of fate.
I believe everything,
even drinking with you,
all of it is connected somehow.
You'll soon understand.
That's only the deception of the drink.
Reality is a bleak world full of
nothing but lust and greed.
There are no connections between people.
Only isolation...
I...
Can't...
Go on...
Victory goes to the young lady!
Thank you!!!
Thank you so much!
You, your stomach bottomless?!
Yahoo!!!
Don't mind me...
Upon first glance,
there were only couples sitting
alongside the Kamo River.
They're so evenly spaced,
is there some rule in place here?
So chilly...
Don't talk nonsense,
you don't find it humid?
Thank you...
What do we have here?
A flyer for the Evening Used Book Market.
That's still going on?
Suddenly, I was being pulled through
time by all the books I'd read,
and I was drawn back to my old
picture book, Ra Ta Ta Tam.
A story about a small white train,
I would ride its rails to go on adventures
outside the bounds of my cramped room.
How did I ever manage to lose a
book as wonderful as that one?
I set out to lay eyes on it once again!
You're awake?
This is the School Festival Executive Office.
This used to be HQ for the Library Police,
an organization made to collect
overdue library books from students.
Furnished with the latest
in surveillance equipment,
every single piece of information
on our students is gathered here.
The work of the School Festival
Executive is indeed taxing --
To ensure our merry fools of students
make a soft landing with harsh reality,
we keep firm grip on every detail
of their desires and actions,
anticipating every one of their next moves.
So why I am here...?
You don't mean!
You've...
That's right.
Naturally, we've collected info on her as well.
- Profile
- Books Borrowed
- Convenience Store Purchases
- Video Rentals
- Diary
- Letters Sent
This...
This is...!!!
This is illegal, isn't it!!!
So you DON'T want to know?
I suppose you'd call this an exchange,
but I was hoping you would help
me out of friendship regardless.
There are just so many troublemakers,
and I'm anxious about our
capability to crack down.
The girl is a fan of a book
named Ra Ta Ta Tam --
Ever since reading it as a girl,
the book has acted as her guiding light,
and it seems she's suddenly remembered it.
RA
TA
M
Where can I get my
hands on that book?
There are many options
for both old and new copies,
from online auctions to bookstores
of several shapes and sizes...
However, the exact copy she had as a child
has just reappeared on
the market as a used book.
Th-That's...
Here.
It's expected to appear at the
Shimogamo Evening Used Book Market.
If you were to obtain this, it would
be quite easy to claim her heart!
Used Book Festival
This was exactly like a sea of books!
I was a fish in the deepest depths,
migrating this way and
that in search of prey!
Birds, Beasts, and Relatives
By: Gerald Durrell
Viva, beginner's luck!
Why is it still so damn
hot this time of night?!
I can't stand used books.
Used books call out in deceit,
"Read us and obtain knowledge!"
but never once have I put any of
that knowledge to practical use.
What I need now isn't knowledge,
but grace and charm!
THEN perhaps we can
talk about knowledge --
What did you do?!
I demand reparations!!!
That's what I'm entitled to say here!
You don't see you're the one
who needs to apologize?
Hmmph, you've got your
mind focused on that girl, huh?
What?!
"If I get my hands on her beloved book,"
"it'll be a cinch to claim her heart."
At least, that's what
you're thinking, right...?
Th-That's TOO on the nose!
If one suddenly finds the book
they've spent years searching for,
or when one remembers
a book from their past
and it appears out of
nowhere in front of them,
I can feel the pull of the thread of fate.
Almost like there is a
God of the Used Book Market,
one who can fashion a happy
encounter with the book I desire,
one who can bring me back to
forgotten books from my past...
At least, that was my gut feeling.
But Ra Ta Ta Tam was
nowhere to be found.
I suppose even the God of the Used Book
Market needs a day off sometimes.
I'm feelin' the same as you...
I'm not findin' the books I really want.
Some nasty collector's got
a tight grip on the rare stuff.
You heard me?
Y'know, way back when,
books traveled from person to person!
A book is reborn
each time it's passed on,
it's one of the things
that ties us together.
But it's like that damn collector's put
up a dam to stop the flow of books.
DAM
Holdin' shadowy auctions
for all his rare books...
Only fools who don't
value their lives take part.
Quite the terrible thing...
Ah! Wait! You stupid brat!
You yanked off the price tags! Stop!
Stop, I said, STOP!!!
Stop, c'mon stop, I said!
Damn that stupid kid...
Getting ice cream all over my pants...
But at least that's all over with now...
Hey kid, give it up already!!!
Huh?! The heck?
What the hell is this?!
This guy's the one
who made me do it!!!
If I didn't, he said he
was gonna molest me!!!
So I...
Hey you.
Why don't you come with me.
H-Hold on! Wait!
I didn't do...
He was going to molest that child...
Hope you like prison, kid.
I'm sure I won't!!!
Hey!
Where'd that brat go?!
What's goin' on here, kid?
Dealin' with another
pants problem, huh?
Yo!
You wanna drink?
An ice kotatsu, how refined!
Higuchi-san, did you really
read all of these books?
Heaven forbid!
I'm selling these to acquaintances
of mine for quite the mark-up.
I must express my gratitude for books.
To think people would pay so handsomely
for nothing more than paper stained with ink.
Anyone who collects dirty things
like those is a total moron!
Today I had quite the harvest.
If you're interested, I'll treat
you to some yakisoba as well.
Thank you so much!
Higuchi treating someone?
That's once every 25 years!
My, it appears even more
profit is on the table.
I have another matter to attend to,
please wait here for my return.
Sure!
This guy here's Don Underwear.
He's quite the hardcore romanticist!
I am no romanticist.
Just...
Someone toiling to once
again meet their fated love.
See what I mean?
It sounds like there's a story there!
It was during last year's School Festival...
After watching a
friend's trifle of a play,
I took seat on a bench...
A rain of apples began
to fall from the sky.
Apples?
Most likely, some students were
transporting them to make apple candy,
and they spilled simultaneously
on the floors above.
And so, down below,
at the same time,
apples bounced off both our heads.
At that moment, it was like my
heart was shot from my chest!
There was no doubt it was love!
Surely, this must have been fate.
However...
I had no idea about
what I should do next.
Our connection was only based
on simultaneous apple thumps,
and so I hesitated
in calling out to her.
And ever since she left...
Not a day has gone by where
I haven't thought of her.
If only I could see her once again,
I would not give in to hesitation!
However, I had no idea on
how to search for her.
I could not trust gossip and
hearsay enough to rely on it.
Everything was chance arranged by fate,
the entire incident had
the flair of the romantic!
I told he was a romantic...
And thus, I went to Yoshida
Shrine and I made my vow.
Until the day I laid eyes on her again...
Until then, I would never
remove this pair of underwear!
Wow!
I think you got some wires
crossed in that head of yours...
Thank you so much!
Thanks ain't necessary.
I got connections.
Well then, I'll...
The ol' koi nursery's
starting to rally again,
so I'm rebuilding my
erotic art collection.
Well isn't that nice!
Well, I'll see you later...
There's a shadowy auction goin' on tonight,
and a legendary piece by
Katsushika Hokusai is on the list.
But wouldn't y'know,
they're holdin' it somewhere
I'm not really welcome.
Ah well, you see...
I saved you, didn't I?
Consider this give-and-take.
Higuchi's there, too...!
I'll wait here! Go on ahead!
I'm beggin' ya!
I'll get ya a nice reward!
I'm countin' on ya! Good luck!
So... What the heck is going on here?
This is a feast for demons,
take care you don't
end up on the menu...
All right, tonight's participants...
If you'll come this way.
This is how Rihaku-san likes it.
What's with the atmosphere here?!
A humble welcome to my festival!
I suppose this is what
you'd call a HOT pot.
If you add some sesame oil,
you'll find it's delicious.
My eyes...!
To whoever lasts the longest at my table,
I shall grant the right to take whichever
book they please off my shelf.
I trust all of you have a choice in mind.
The manuscript of
the Kokinshu!
The diary of Ryusei Kishida
is my white whale.
The Steam Train/Steamship
Trip Guide 1st Edition!
The erotic art
by Hokusai!!!
And this is a picture book belonging to a
certain raven-haired girl when she young.
Have a look, her name is
written right on it.
All right, Romantic Engine,
full speed ahead!
It's Ra Ta Ta Tam...
Not only that, the one
she had as a child, too!
That makes it the most valuable
thing under the heavens!
Now then, your first course...
How about you all begin
with one piece each.
SPICY...!!!
Hey now, little boy!
You mustn't be naughty!
I'm not being naughty!
I'm doing something good here!
Something good?
Hey miss, did you know?
Every book is connected.
For example, that girl has
the entire Sherlock Holmes.
The author, Conan Doyle.
Getting inspiration from
the French author Jules Verne,
he wrote the science-fiction
novel "The Lost World".
Now look at the book over there.
That's Mathias Sandorf, written by Verne
out of respect to Alexandre Dumas.
Dumas' work, "The Count of Monte Cristo", came
to Japan under the name "The Cavern King".
The first to adapt it was Ruiko Kuroiwa
of the Yorozu Morning News.
And he in turn appeared as a character in
the novel "The Meiji Tower of Babel".
The author of that was Futaro Yamada.
In his "War Generation Anti-War Diaries",
Yamada declared the novel
"Oni Fire" to be utter rubbish.
That was written
by Seishi Yokomizo.
He was an editor at the
magazine "Shin Seinen" in his youth,
and his co-editor at the time was On Watanabe, author of "The Androgynous Scion."
Jun'ichiro Tanazaki submitted an article titled
"Harusamu" to honor him after his death.
Tanazaki engaged in fierce literary
dispute with Ryunosuke Akutagawa.
Months after the dispute,
Akutagawa took his own life.
Hyakken Uchida explored the
particulars of this suicide in "Bowler Hat."
This work was then
praised by Yukio Mishima.
At the age of 22, Mishima declared his hatred of Osamu Dazai directly to Dazai's face.
After losing his friend to tuberculosis,
Dazai wrote an article in his memoriam,
the author of that book there,
Sakunosuke Oda.
All books are connected, this Sea of
Used Books is in truth one giant book!
You... What on earth are you?
I'm the God of the Used Book Market!
I offer divine wrath to those who stop
the flow of books by locking them away,
my duty is to return those books
back to the sea they came from!
And that's why I'd like
you to help me, miss.
You're certainly packing it away!
If you tire of the hot pot,
we also have ramen and gyoza!
Don't you think it's
about time you gave up?
Right back at you.
Perhaps it's best to quit if you're
hallucinating rainbow streamers...
I bet you're seeing them too,
why not worry about yourself?
I had already forgotten pain.
My consciousness had grown dim.
Intent only on defeating
the hot pot in front of me,
I was now a perpetual motion machine.
You're persistent, aren't you...
No one yet's been able to
hold out as long as I have...
I'm starting to hallucinate things like this.
My hallucination's not
going to lose to yours!!!
Bravo!
Young man, you are the victor!
Take your book and go!
Thank you so, so much...
Huh?!
What's this?
It is I, God of the Used Book Market!
That kid!!!
Imprudent collector,
reap what you have sown!
- The Steam Train/Steamboat Trip Guide!
- The manuscript for the Kokinshu!!!
If you want them, go trove
the Sea of Used Books!
I believe you'll find them in
appropriate places at appropriate prices.
Damn it all to hell!
My collection!!!
Stop!!! My future is waiting!!!
Isn't that...
...the Senpai I keep bumping into?
Hey, miss! Thanks a lot!
Those books have been resurrected.
I bet you'll come across
Ra Ta Ta Tam any minute now!
Th-This is the diary of Ryusei Kishida!
Why is it here?!
Never mind, I'm so grateful!
-The manuscript of the Kokinshu!
- The Steam Train/Steamboat Trip Guide!
How unfortunate...
To be betrayed by the
God of the Used Book Market.
How utterly annoying.
Then I'll treat you
to yakisoba instead!
Hanuki-san, maybe you best go home...
This way!
- Hey ho...
- Hey ho!
What's this?
Guerrilla theater.
It's time for the School Festival already?
The Eccentric King! Scene 47!
You there! Are you Jogasaki,
the head of the Film Club Misogi?
How dare you address me without "-san"!
Tell me your name this instant!
I am Princess Daruma!
I'm searching for the Eccentric King,
now tell me where he is!
No, Kaori!!!
You bitch...
That's utterly low!
Kyoto University President's
Special Curry
If I were to cover this thing in curry
and leave it for the Mt. Yoshida stray dogs
Oh, how much fun that would be!
Stop this now, don't you dare
treat Kaori as a mere object
For I do not know
Where to find the Eccentric King
And that is the honest truth
However...!
However?
- If you don't spit it out...
- Stop, please!!!
Oh, my beloved Eccentric King
Where can I find him now
The School Festival Executive Director knows...
The Executive Director knows?
Your compatriot in Breast Rock Climbing,
your friend from the
Bedchamber Investigation Team?
Yes, the one who gave me
handholds shaped like breasts,
my friend and rival in Breast Rock Climbing!
My junior in the Bedchamber Investigation Team,
The School Festival Executive Director knows...
You, with your obsessive clean freak tendencies
You who will never accept
intimacy with real flesh and blood!
Acknowledge the filthiness of your own soul
And apply some bleach
Finally, I know the villain
The mastermind is revealed
My enemy is none other than the
School Festival Executive Director!
Kaori!!!
Take it down, guys!
Hey ho!
Stop right there!
Guerrilla theater is a violation of the rules!
- Hey ho!
You public moral flouting scoundrels!
Stop!
It appears that your presence has
extended the night somewhat.
I'll watch over Hanuki,
you can be on your way.
We'll meet at the School Festival.
Okay!
And I recommend buying
some ajari-mochi on your way.
It's quite delicious when it's fresh.
And so, I made my way
towards the School Festival.
This night was far from over!
A school festival is a high
pressure bargain sale of youth --
A Midnight Market of Youthfulness!
Ra Ta Ta Tam Shop
No Touching
A picture book?
There's just one?
Hey, now!
No window shopping.
There were no more obstacles in my path!
I'd obtained a key item
needed to enter the citadel.
All I needed to do now was wait for
the raven-haired maiden to appear!
This is Ra Ta Ta Tam!
Such a coincidence!
This is no coincidence!
This is inevitability!
And thus we'd finally talk...
About love, about our futures!
My long battle is on the
verge of drawing to a close!
Already I smile and grow nostalgic
upon reflection of this journey...
- Over there!
- Hey ho!
Hey, stop it!
Don't you "Hey ho" me!
What are you doing?!
That was my stall, damn it!
Wait!
The Eccentric King!
Hey!
Damn it, they're quick...
What the heck was that about?
You! We group up at headquarters!
They're a School Festival terrorist
group intent on guerrilla theater.
They steal the frameworks of unpopular
festival stalls and use them to build stages.
Their play is "The Eccentric King."
It's an adventure musical,
about Princess Daruma's search
for the eponymous king.
Eccentric King Stage Locations
Revelations about students
and clubs are woven into the story,
making a mix of truth and fiction,
and those who've had their dirty secrets
revealed have fallen hard from grace.
Leaving this group unchecked for so long
has placed our reputation on the line!
The Eccentric King must be stopped!
We must return order to the School Festival!
Yes, sir!
Director!
Director, what should we do
about the Swift-Footed Kotatsu?
That's lower on the priority list.
Swift-Footed Kotatsu Locations
However, they're treating
passerbys to helpings of hot pot!
Left unchecked,
food poisoning is a possibility...
I'll leave that to you.
Must be rough...
My goodness, everyone everywhere
is running roughshod!
You're sick?
I picked it up at
another of my affairs...
Congratulations!
Your prize is this red carp backpack!
Just put your arms
through here to wear it!
Here!
Cool, ain't it!
My back was now nice and warm!
To get this red carp just
as I was getting chilly...
Three cheers for opportunism!
Hail and amen!
Truly, this was a theater of youth.
Over 18 Only!
Jogasaki's Cherished Love Doll!
There were so many splendid works
by talented students on display...
Mr. Jogasaki's Breast Rock Climbing!
Each flowed by like illustrations
from some fantastic picture book.
Kyoufuku Railways
Pretty Girl Crane Game
You sure can drink!
I'm not done yet!
Rice Fundamentalists vs. Bread Alliance
Rice! Or Wheat!
Well, what about cookies!
Those are like bread!
If you believe that nonsense,
then rice crackers are a type of rice!
My, that's a splendid red carp you have.
Higuchi-san!
This time it's a warm kotatsu, huh?
Would you care for some hot pot?
We're on the run from the
School Festival Executive.
The stakes sure have risen...
Please put your mind at ease.
While my underwear remains on,
I shall not go under the kotatsu.
How admirable.
Such is the etiquette
required of Don Underwear.
He's about to undertake
the greatest battle of his life.
Please, watch and enjoy!
I shall be leading the entire School
Festival to a happy ending for sure!
Still, not having changed
underwear for so long,
I'm surprised you're even still alive...
I did immediately get sick.
But yet I still heartily live!
It's the Swift-Footed Kotatsu!
Hold it right there!
Time to go...
- Hey ho...
- Hey ho!
Stop!
Over here!
The Princess isn't coming!
She's been caught!
Already?!
There's no backup!
You do it, then!
Heck no!
Hey, you!
You wanna be an actress?
Whatever, you're doing it.
Here's your script!
We can feed you your lines, too.
Unnecessary! I've memorized it all.
I shan't tuck my tail
between my legs and run!
It must be fate that I've been
handed such a major role!
I've resolved to follow my
thread of fate until the end!
You got your cold from that
Obscene Investigation Team, did you not?
It's not the Obscene Investigation Team!
The Bedchamber Investigation Team!
Bedchamber, you mean a lady's bedroom!
Investigation there is done only
by the indecent and shameless!
The name Depraved Director suits you well!
That reprehensible sickness you bear
To such baseness, I shall never yield
Until the day
My beloved Eccentric King
I lay eyes on you again
That Eccentric King of yours
Imprisonment was his fate
Never again set to return
Neither his name nor his ideals
Even if the path I follow
Should lead me straight to the depths of hell
Never shall I become plagued by doubt or fear
Ever onward, I'll press forward
If it's for the sake of the Eccentric King!
The Eccentric King Players!
Performing a play here violates the rules!
- Surrender yourselves quietly!
- Take it down, guys!
Let the show go on,
you pain-in-the-ass!
Don't give me your cold,
Depraved Director!
Stop this!
Out of my way!
Again?!
Why are you always front stage center?!
They escaped our clutches once again!
They have an 11th leading lady!
Go ahead and keep catching us!
Our reserves are limitless!
Be that as it may, the latest
one is lacking in acting ability.
It seems you must be running out.
However, it's strange!
The script appears freshly written,
but we have yet to find the author!
If we capture the author,
continuing the play will be an impossibility.
Where are they...
Director!
Hey, Director!
We've just intercepted a text message!
- That's private!!!
- It's the latest script!
We've confiscated their new lyrics!
Also, this poster was amongst the data!
What on earth...
The final scene is up next!
A Love Scene Grand Finale?
L-L-L-Love Scene?!
But where?!
Please watch this security footage!
The Swift-Footed Kotatsu...
Wait, what's that?
A daruma?
Forgotten by the Swift-Footed Kotatsu?
If we rewind...
So that's what's going on!
How could I not have noticed?
You! Bring up the Eccentric King map!
Now overlay the Swift-Footed Kotatsu map!
It's a perfect match!
So the ringleaders of
"The Eccentric King",
they write the script at the kotatsu,
and once they move, the troupe
performs at their old location!
Shit...
The Swift-Footed Kotatsu is on the
move through the courtyard!
It's Higuchi and Don Underwear!
- The Don...?!
- Depraved Director!!!
Everyone everywhere is
running roughshod...!!!
Chase that kotatsu!
Don Underwear must not
take the stage at all costs!!!
What's up next?
Well, there's a love scene up next,
between you and Don Underwear.
You fine with that?
I may have no experience,
but I'm ready and willing
to answer drama's call!
Don Underwear put on this play to
search for an unrequited love.
If this play becomes hot topic on campus,
his Apple Girl will definitely come watch!
Don Underwear will lay his
feelings bare once she appears!
The fact the King and
the Princess can't meet,
it's a metaphor for his current situation!
There's no way she won't respond
to the Don's feelings of love!
Then that means for sure!
Until our Apple Girl appears,
the show must go on!
Our connection to the
kotatsu's been leaked!
They'll most likely be
expecting us on the roof!
Tactics O!
There!
If the troupe isn't stopped,
she'll have a love scene in
public with Don Underwear...
This is bad!!!
This is most definitely NOT
the script written in my heart!
Never mind, if I can
just make it to the stage,
I can trade places with the Don...!
The two of us finally being united,
that's drama of the highest order!
Director! We know the kotatsu's location!
My Romantic Engine doesn't
have enough horsepower!
I'm gonna lose MY
final act if this keeps up!
Naoko-san!!!
Naoko-san, I'll Wait For You
Until My Dying Day
Bit-part...
Romantic Engine,
Activate Pure Love Nitro!
If she's tonight's leading lady,
then damn straight I'm going
to be the leading man!
Hey, your belt's all twisted!
Let me fix that for you.
The only thing twisted here
is my love-struck heart!
What are you doing?!
This isn't what you promised!
The girl takes priority over everything else!
That promise is about 5th on my list!
Where's the Eccentric King?!
That was quite the hustle,
yet this isn't the finish line.
The final scene is taking place over there.
The Eccentric King!
Begin!
The Eccentric King
Has vanished, nowhere to be found
And the world
Has been plunged in grief
Yet this time, for sure,
My journey is almost at its end!
This time, for sure...
One day, on a bench
I had taken seat
And you had taken seat nearby
And then, from up above
A rain of apples
And at the moment I saw you
You looked my way as well!
And then, on both our heads...
Out of nowhere, a thump!
Two apples...
Out of nowhere, a thump.
Such a twist of fate
This divine revelation
At that moment, I knew it was love!
Th-That's...!
I adore you
My destined love
Princess...
- Daruma...
- This is a festival of fools.
Keep watching and
you'll become one, too.
If I'm going to be a fool anyway,
Then I'll...
...be a DANCING fool!
Something's caught on the net!
Raise it up!
Music!
I happened to be passing through by chance
But to be able to meet you like this
Is such a marvelous joy
Who's this idiot?!
I'm just a poor seller of Ra Ta Ta Tam
Get lost!
And so, my raven-haired maiden
It is I, the Senpai you often meet
What's this crap?!
The hell?!
Senpai, such a coincidence
No, simply by chance!
Such a coincidence
No, just by chance!
A coincidence
By chance!
- Coinci...
- Chance!
- Coin...
-Co...
- ...ance!
I suppose, then, it must be fate!
Well, time for the kiss.
But this isn't how she really feels...
It's a play, it's out of
dramatic necessity!
Senpai?
I am the one, the leading man
This play's grand conspirator
A disruption, quite unexpected
Just jammed up the works
But please, forget about that now
Keep your eyes focused on me!
Ah! My darling, lovely Apple Girl!
If you're out there, out there somewhere,
Then please, won't you now take the stage!
I suppose you mean me?
Isn't it strange, a coincidence
A thunderclap under blue sky
That once again, in this place
I should lay my eyes on you
Destiny layered in destiny
To think that I, just like you
Had been waiting, oh so long
My person of destiny
By heaven's decree, it's you, Don Underwear!
A-Apple Girl...
It's you...!
Apologies.
Consider yourself caught!
Underwear!
You public moral flouting scoundrel!
I'm the School Festival Executive Director!
Your beloved Apple Girl
was a mere disguise,
an idol I dress up as
for my own amusement!
Though I must apologize for the deceit.
Am I
Just no good
My dear Don Underwear
You were always, always on my mind
Always have I
Been left staring at your back
Supporting you this entire time
However
In your heart
There lives someone different
If all you desire is a woman of beauty
Then cosmetic surgery
Even that, I would consider
Won't you please just look my way!
Do it!
Look her way!
Get lost, Depraved Director!
Go to your Bedchamber!
I'm sorry, but
That's something I just can't do
What I fell in love with
Was not a face, but the thump of an apple
It was at that moment
I knew that my fate had been sealed
Even if
My beloved
Should happen to be a man
This heartbeat of mine
It can tell no lies
You're always going on
about the damn romantic!!!
Look at the girl standing in front of you!
I'm not quite as heartless as people say I am
I long for nothing more than
someone to cure my loneliness
Yet I am the one in charge,
the Executive Director
There is no one
Who could ever understand me
Yet if you were willing to take me in your arms
Then in that case, for you, a woman I can be!
You delirious from fever?!
You're taking opportunism too far!
Just get this over with...!
Just play some music...!
No! Don't drop the curtain!
Seeking another's warmth to
cure transitory loneliness!
Utterly... Preposterous!!!
Yuko! Jirokichi!
My koi...!
These koi
Have birthed a new love
This time for sure, a destined love
Love, ever fickle
Love, ever selfish
But at the end I've finally met you
My one and true destiny
The story, as always, is opportunism
Finally, you looked my way
I know that you
They're alive...
I know they're alive...!
You are my destined love
In our rose-colored campus life!
Before I'd realized it,
I had caught a cold.
- Haven't seen anyone in two weeks
- Some tamagozake would clear this up
- My fridge is empty (T_T)
I muttered out my symptoms on
social media but got no response.
Was everyone still out?
Or was the thought of associating
with me too unbearable.
An evening that seemed to encompass
every season had left me beat...
I doubt I'll be putting away
my bed for some time.
"Alone", by Yumeji Takehisa
I wait for one one, no one waits for me
I wait for no one, no one waits for me...
I wait for no one, no one waits for me!!!
If you're making tamagozake,
leave out the egg and the sugar...
Not going to happen.
You're sick because you
allowed your spirit to falter.
You should follow my example.
Higuchi, you didn't catch a
cold because you're an idiot.
Although I'll admit I'm happy
you dropped by to see me...
If I was laid up with no visitors,
I would likely starve to death.
Though I'm afraid I
can't offer much help...
Thank goodness she's here, too.
This is a lot tastier than I'd expected!
So, how is everyone else?
It seems like the entire
city is fighting off a cold...
If you go outside,
it's almost like a ghost town.
You must be tough if you
haven't caught it yet!
If we had some Junpero,
this epidemic would be over in an instant.
The legendary wonder drug used in the
treatment of tuberculosis ages ago...
When it's swirled on a stick like candy,
one lick can lower any fever.
One's body is fulled to the
brim with vitality once more.
That's right! Rihaku-san
would have some for sure!
I sense another profitable venture ahead...
Oh no, Don Underwear!
Ah... Hey...
I'm wearing new underwear...
F-Finally...
Are you all right?!
Noriko-kun's cold...
It's an awful beast...
I'm off to see her...
That's mutual destruction!
I'll go with you!
There's nothing better if you're sick!
Cola has secret ingredients inside,
and they work well on colds...
If you add some ginger, too...
The effect is increased a hundredfold...
Delicious...
My mother taught me how to make it.
I'd rather the Don not
feel too humiliated,
so keep this our little secret.
Thanks for going out of your way...
But you need to dress
warmer or you'll get sick, too!
Take one of my sweaters, at least.
I'll be fine!
Of course not!
Those round cushions are really cute...
Yeah, but I bought a ton...
But squeezing them feels so nice,
AND they're fun, too.
You know, it's a waste if I'm the
only eating your tamagozake.
Could you bring some to the Director?
He's all by himself, so he's
probably feeling forlorn.
Certainly!
And bring some Ginger Cola with you, too...
Apologies for making
you go out of your way...
As you can see, my new
popularity is burying me alive.
So many people sent you gifts!
My performance in that musical,
it brought me a lot of new
fans from across campus.
So please, don't concern
yourself with me.
However, since I seem to have
given my cold to most of my guests,
it does pain my heart somewhat.
The one I'm most worried about,
it's my Senpai from the Bedchamber
Investigation Team, Todo-san.
His daughter has yet to visit him,
and he must be lonely
wrapped up in bed by himself.
I'll go visit him.
Really?
There's some apples over there,
would you mind bringing some with?
An apple a day and all that...
Yes!
A tornado ruined the crop last year,
but this year it's been quite the harvest.
I also received a bunch of hats,
so please, help yourself.
Your ears do look quite cold.
So, what happened afterwards?
With the Senpai you keep bumping into,
on the stage of the Eccentric King.
That was...!
He was just passing through by chance.
Really now! That was
quite the hijack he pulled.
He is my friend, after all,
and that was the first time
I'd ever seen him so frantic.
But I suppose you wouldn't understand.
You always press forward, paying no
mind to those left in your wake.
The fact you bumped
into him so frequently...
You didn't find it strange?
Up to this point, I had given
myself over to wonder,
following the road
wherever it lead.
I had been lax in forging the tactics
required for romantic relationships,
and noticing the feelings of
others was quite beyond me.
I suppose trying to grasp my own fluffy
cotton-candy feelings was difficult as well.
But, when I remember Senpai wrapping his
arms around my papier mache costume,
something inside of me goes "Pop!",
and I want nothing more
than to glomp my red carp.
Yahoo!
Did I actually manage
to achieve anything?
It was all just my
imagination, wasn't it...
Yahoo...
Even coughing -- I am alone.
Ozaki Hosai
What dragged you
all the way out here?
The Executive Director
told me where you live.
I thought he was pissed at me...
I did give him this cold, after all.
It seems he was more worried
about you than himself.
My daughter did come to visit,
but she ended up gettin' my cold...
I bet she's gonna pass it on to
her husband and her new in-laws...
Heck, you might end up gettin' it too.
It seems the God of Colds
and I are on the outs.
For pete's sake...
Here you are lookin' out for me again.
Hey, I met some kid searchin' for
some old book at the market,
he your Senpai?
He wanted some lousy kid's
book called Ra Ta Ta Tam...
Seems he wanted to get
his hands on it at any cost.
Even though I begged him to
get me that piece of erotic art...
Whatever, I ended up gettin'
my hands on it anyway.
Oh yeah, not for nothin',
I got this cold from Rihaku-san.
He already had it back
at your drinking contest,
and it sounds like it's
only got worse since then.
Oh!
Why are the streets so deserted today?
This cold lays in ambush attacking
anyone who approaches.
I thought the world got destroyed
while I was wrapped up in bed.
Oh, you won't believe this!
Higuchi-kun finally got sick, too!
I had planned on visiting Rihaku-san,
but the closer I got,
the more the wind lost mercy.
Alas, my attempt at the
journey was left in tragic defeat.
This is no mere common cold...
This retrovirus gone rampant is
none other than the Rihaku Cold!
May I ask you where Rihaku-san lives?
He parks his train in an isolated
area by Takaragaike Lake,
where winds are constantly gushing out.
The God of Colds inside of
Rihaku sends forth its minions,
and the wind sends them
swirling through Kyoto!
If we do nothing, this ends in double
suicide between Kyoto and Rihaku!
I'm on my way to go visit Rihaku-san now!
Look what happened to
Higuchi when he tried!
There must be some reason the God of
Colds wants nothing to do with me...
This must be fate as well.
There's something I must go
tell Rihaku-san in person!
Apologies for dropping in so late!
Rihaku-san!
Rihaku-san!!!
I'm on my deathbed...
You mustn't give in so easily!
It seems you haven't changed...
How many decades have passed
since our drinking contest...
It hasn't been that long.
It was only a few hours ago,
this very night!
Then I suppose that's good.
Time in isolation flies like an arrow,
it seemed like vast expanses
of time had gone by....
On such a lonely winter's night,
I'm weeping like an infant
with a soiled diaper.
No matter how much I wail,
my mother doesn't appear...
But yet I'm here!
I used to love collecting and
trading valuable milk caps.
In Sevens, I loved ensuring play
can't continue past 6 or 8,
and I reveled in drinking in
everyone's troubled faces.
My parents wanted little to
do with me, but I had money,
and with money came friends.
Then women, then more money.
However...
There were those who stole
what I had through brute force,
and in the end I had nothing.
I knew then the world was a scramble,
full of nothing but taking...
But strength, that could be
bought with money too.
So could love.
There is nothing on earth
that money can't buy.
Yet...
No matter how much I collected,
my heart remained unfulfilled.
Rihaku-san, you're not alone.
Of course you're connected to others!
The money you loaned out to
people became their strength,
and after having their fun,
they returned to you once again.
Your cold was first transferred to Hanuki-san,
then to Todo-san and the Director,
The Don, Noriko-san, and all their friends,
and then to friends of those friends...
It's spreading all throughout the city!
The things you stole,
they bounced from one place to the next,
bringing happiness with them.
Even as you profess your isolation,
you're still to bound to others in the end.
The thread of fate you weave with,
everyone is connected to,
whether they like it or not.
Rihaku-san, you're absolutely not alone!
This evening was all thanks to you...
A long and wondrous,
marvelous night!
Thank you...
Thanks to you, Rihaku-san,
I had such a wonderful evening.
The Fake Denki Bran was quite delicious.
So...
Shall we have some more, then?
I'll drink until there's nothing left.
What's that?
It appears there's a virus out
there even worse than what I had...
A terminal case if I ever saw one.
A young man is struggling with
isolation to a greater degree than I did.
Would you perhaps have
an idea who it could be?
Now that I think of it,
someone does come to mind...
Do you remember the
story Ra Ta Ta Tam?
That small white train
had a destination in mind...
Just as you have a final
station to approach as well.
Yes!
The dawn is drawing near...
The night is short!
Walk on, young girl!
This cold medicine will cure the incurable!
It's Junpero!
Destination
Life is indeed short, my dear
So, young lady, do fall in love
Nothing changed after
coming to university.
All that came were grades that
held no promise for the future.
I could delay the
inevitable with grad school,
but it'll all end in
a job hunt, anyway.
Not clever, not talented.
Not financially stable,
not strong, not determined.
Not charismatic, not a charming piglet
boy one wants to rub cheeks with.
Just an eternal string of "I'm nots".
There's no way I can
make it in this world.
Where Is My Talent Hidden?
Spending all that time rushing about
wondering where my talent lies...
A Skilled Hawk Hides Its Talons
It's almost like back
when I was a freshman,
I stored away a talent
piggy bank in my closet.
Wait, did that really happen?!
It must have!
Everyone Starts Somewhere...
So Just Start
Everyone quiet!
Why Are We Now Stuck On
"The Eternal Obstacle Removing Plan"?
It's been a year since we met her!
We were on the verge of
removing every obstacle in our path,
so why do we now have the
"Eternal Obstacle Removing Plan"?
We could not ascertain
her true feelings!
A detestable lack
of determination!
Our good name is in ruins,
we need to revise!
Revise? As in claim we
no longer desire her?
If we do, our good
name is preserved!
I can't acknowledge this!
We claim to be head over heels,
yet we know nothing about her!
Nothing apart from the image of the
back of her head seared into our retinas.
We use the girl as an excuse!
A coward's plot to
fill the abyss in our heart!
We should all be ashamed!
We must grovel before her!
Fine, go get all red-faced
and pouty like a damn daruma.
Don't be swept away by the tide!
The world holds a prejudice that
students must have sweethearts!
Thus, we foolish students hold that to heart,
and recklessly rush for social status,
and then unnaturally,
we all have sweethearts!
In that case, all we do is
encourage that same prejudice!
I oppose! Resolutely!
All we want is to no
longer to be alone!
Coward! Grit your teeth!
All we do is run away since
we can't predict the future!
We need to find
out how she feels!
But we must do it as
discreetly as possible!
Let me in there!!!
I gotta take part!!!
Stop this! We must
think rationally!
Are we even capable of
something as delicate as dating?
Dating, sounds fun...
All you want us to do
is cop a feel or two!
You mean to say our mind
is that utterly obscene?
Yes, our mind does
hold some indecency,
but that's not
all it holds!
So many other things,
even beautiful things!
OPEN THE DAMN DOOR!
What if we get smashed
to smithereens?
As if we could arrange
a date in the first place!
If she had drawn close that night,
could we have even handled it?
She wouldn't! She's not
some sleazy instant ramen girl!
So if she invited us to cop a feel,
we would have refused?
Perhaps not...
How many times have
you looked, you lech?
We must bow and repent!
Go get your kicks from
feeling up rubber balls then!
Fallacious, utterly fallacious...
Why do we idolize her, anyway?!
Why her?!
Make a convincing argument
if we're to continue!
Coward!
Betrayer!
Fool!
Pervert!
Thoughtless!!!
Reckless!!!
Everyone quiet!
Gentlemen, however!
If we're having this
thorough of a discussion,
let us consider how
relationships even start.
Gentlemen, this pure start to love you
all seek doesn't exist to begin with!
The more we mull over and
analyze every possible component,
the more our feet get
rooted, frozen in place!
Lust, vanity, fad, delusion, foolishness...
we become utterly engulfed!
There comes a time when we
must risk leaping into darkness,
even if we end up plunging
into the hell of heartbreak!!!
As if we could
really do it!
If we don't jump, our future is clear!
We'll just continue to spin in circles
in some corner of our wasted youth!!!
We will never lay bare our feelings for her!
I ask, if we died tomorrow, would
any of you truly have no regrets?!
If so, step forward right now!!!
The girl is on her way.
I told her where you live.
It can't be...
That young lady will be
here any moment now.
A Girl Who Goes to
Visit All Her Sick Friends?
Fushimi
Visiting Naoko and Her Husband
Swimming up the stream of the night's events,
I visited everyone wishing for their quick recovery,
A Feverish Passion Without the Fever
but they worried for me as much as I did for them,
She Receives Some Boiled Kabocha
and in the end they sent me off bearing several gifts.
I did feel left out since I was the only one not sick...
Visiting Akagawa With Lots of
Rhetoric Club Members
The Girl Recieves Dried Plums
It was an odd sort of loneliness.
The Couple at the Bookstore Feel Better
If I wouldn't be alone,
I felt that perhaps a cold wouldn't be so bad.
She Receives Asadaame Cough Drops
Kantaro, the Boy of the North Winds!
A Big Success!!
She's getting closer by the second!
She's on her way here?!
Take shelter!!!
Maybe we SHOULD
just open the gates?
You dare suggest exposing
her to our filthy soul?!
The best defense
is offense!
Activate the
Defensive Shutdown!
But she DID come
all this way...
We're just not ready!
We will NEVER be ready!
Return the obstacles!!!
Don't panic, gentlemen!
Calm down!
We have to keep the gates sealed!!!
Open up! We're taking over!!!
You, get the HELL OUT!!!
We're breaking through!
We'll spread our arms open
wide and invite her in!!!
- Where the hell's the switch?
- Stop it!!!
This area is under Defensive Shutdown.
This area --
Just give your body over to instinct!
Quick!!! Hide!!!
Senpai?
Where on earth are you?
Senpai!
Buy us some time!
- How'm I gonna do that?
- Whatever, just DO something!!!
- Senpai...
- Master! Get ready to jump!
No, no!!! I'm just not ready yet!
What'll happen if I die?!
Master! You have to go now!
I don't wanna...!!!
Shoot! Shoot her down now!
You flew down to save me!
Yeah, I guess I finally did!
Senpai!
Shouldn't we be looking
at this wondrous scenery?
I'm already looking at something wondrous!
Besides, this is the only way
wings shaped like these can fly!
Are you all right?
Y... Yeah...
I guess... I'm getting there...
You weren't quite lucid
but I came up anyway.
Apologies...
Wait, is that...?
Ra Ta Ta Tam!
You can take it if you'd like.
This is exactly the one
I had when I was young!
This is my name written on here!
Well, I just happened upon it by chance.
Thank you so, so much...
I'll treasure it forever...
You did come all this way.
I was just passing through by chance...
Well, that's quite a coincidence.
Oh yeah, I hear there's a great
used book shop close by...
Perhaps, we could go together...
Gladly!
A cold...
It seems I've caught a cold, too.
What if she doesn't come?
Wait, what if she DOES come?
I want to go back to those carefree
days I was removing obstacles!!!
I'm ashamed to admit I couldn't
sleep past 6 this morning.
He had suggested we go for coffee
before we went to the used book shop.
Hey wait, is this actually a date?!
After gathering my scattered thoughts,
I finally found a thread of conversation.
In truth, there was something
I wanted to ask her!
Just what kind of night she had in Pontocho...
At the used book market...
The school festival...
Visiting the sick...
Just what was she doing that whole time?
A mysterious night that
seemed to span an entire year...
If she would be kind enough to
tell me about her exploits,
I would respond with
the memories of mine.
That's right, there's something
I really wanted to ask Senpai!
Just what kind of night he had in Pontocho...
At the used book market...
The school festival...
Sick in bed...
Just where he traveled to on
that mysterious night...
That's what I'd really like to find out!
Welcome!
For us to have met like this...
It must have been fate!
That girl kicked her skateboard
And went flying down Main Street
The lazy darkness shines bright
As it slides down into the gutters
Standing on their tiptoes yet falling short,
Those boys shake the world
Platitudes like "Be true to yourself!",
They tear them up and throw them aside
Take all of your vague, unprompted sadness
And jam it down into your knees
Stand alone out in the wilderness
Then head off somewhere, staggering to and fro
Swaying, swaying, keep pressing onward
No matter where you go
No matter where you go!
No matter where you go...
Let the blazing lights of downtown
Set fire to the depths of your heart
Stand alone at the edge of the world
Head off somewhere, staggering to and fro
Swaying, swaying, keep pressing onward
No matter where you go
No matter where you go!
No matter where you go...
After three
Backwards
Somersaults
the sad clown failed to stick the landing
His face
Did seem
Quite clouded
Like seeing the sky behind a row of fluttering flags
I guess I'll pray
For his
Health and safety
But still, who's gonna pray for us?
That girl kicked her skateboard
And went flying down Main Street
The distance between us closed before I realized it
And slowly but surely
An unexpected future beckons
So go sing, and go dance!
La Lu La Lu La!!!
Take all of your vague unprompted sadness
And jam it down into your knees
Stand alone out in the wilderness
Head out somewhere, staggering to and fro
Swaying, swaying, keep pressing onward
No matter where you go
No matter where you go!
No matter where you go...
That girl kicked her skateboard
And went flying down Main Street
The lazy darkness shines bright
As it slides down into the gutters
La Lu La Lu La...
La Lu La Lu La!!!
La Lu La Lu La
Brought to you by MaruChanSubs
Hope you enjoyed!